SWATI CHAUDHARY

CONTACTS



New Delhi, Dwarka



Swatichaudhary9000@gmail.com



9654844840

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Experienced in order to cash as senior analyst over 5+ years' experience in various ERP systems. My philosophy is to build and develop the strongest talent possible. I am a true believer in change management who holds a core belief in knowledge transfer and knowledge sharing. Extensive experience in two successful transition process, working with internal & external business partners and customer services.

WORK EXPERIENCE

JOHNSON CONTROLS INC - (MAR 2022 TO DEC 2022)

Senior contract analyst

- Excellent understand of the transition process landscape
- Work under tight timeframes and meet the stake holder expectations
- Influence relevant stake holders and Service owners in adherence to transition process compliance
- Outstanding ability to read and interpret contract documents and understand business concepts
- Ensured vendor and supplier business and legal terms are accurately documented
- Coordinating with legal team whenever contracts seem risky in legal perspective
- Modification in the master contracts in respect of accounting changes
- Verifying the customer's creditworthiness through the DNBI portal ensures better cash flow that the customer has in backup to pay off the contract value.
- Approving the prepayment discounts on the contracts

Accenture India Private Limited – (Oct 2020 to Feb 2022)

Senior Process Analyst (OTC)

- Expertise in the sales and distribution module.
- Worked on diverse billing processes depending on the business needs, such as order-related billing, delivery-related billing, resource-related billing, milestone billing, and periodic billing.
- Sales Order Management: Master data & organizational units, order to cash business sales order processing, shipping, billing, repo
- Experience in inventory management such as goods receipt, goods issue, movement types, transfer postings, and special stocks
- Working with various delivery document types, delivery item categories, shipping point determination, route determination, and picking location determination
- Experience with other SAP modules or technologies would be advantageous, especially PS-WBS element creation, blanket orders, purchase orders, and pulling reports.

TRUE NORTH AR PVT. LTD - (MAY 2017 TO SEPT 2020)

Associate ANALYST (Cash application & Billing)

- Communicated with clients to review and verify client billing requirements
- distributed workflow and audited invoices, ensuring quality of work.
- Ensured bills were submitted within the allowable timeframe and followed up on A/R reports
- Reconcile discrepancies between the accounts receivable general ledger account and the accounts receivable trial balance account.
- Monitor payments due from clients and promptly contacted clients with past due payments
- Posting of customer payments based on different client's payment files and posting criteria
- Preparing Monthly Reports and Invoices on collection activities
- Closure of the accounts on the basis of the status of the account (PIF or SIF) and on client request
- QC of the client report and update or change the invoices

SKILLS

- Account Receivables (O2C)
- SAP FICO, SD
- Billing & Collections
- MS-OFFICE (ACCESS, WORD, EXCEL, POWER POINT
- Basic computer Knowledge like Internet, use of peripherals of computer

EDUCATION

• Bachelor of Commerce (Delhi University 2008

Passed Executive Level ICSI
2009

• Intermediate passed from C.B.S.E board 2005